The latest event, Treasure Month, Team Upright is so awesome! 1. Starting from the 8th, log in and complete simple tasks.
You can get the prostitution legend bundle for free,
They are S R M U Z I A K twelve Tesla star signs,
Tang Long 932A salvaged some wristbands, M Yaoliu G3 Victor's hunting moment.
You can choose two out of three according to your preferences. Second, the dam's long-term workers are eight ten.
New treasure points will be added, which need to be opened through the treasure map. You can see it through the official PV,
They are all fighting for the same one. All treasure hiding spots should be fixed, and the locations of the big pillars should be in these places.
Among them, point No. 8 is bound to be red. So be careful at this point, be careful not to be posted by me.
Then the method to obtain the treasure map is very simple. The first way is to redeem the treasure map fragments;
The second is to obtain it in the game. The probability of getting a suitcase should be higher. three
During the airdrop event, the entire map will be refreshed with airdrops. According to my past experience,
The popularity of this was outrageous when the event first came out.
Moreover, the BGM airdropped now is a theme specially created by "L Worker" for "Treasure Page"
The song is very nice. With so many activities, I might earn 100 million a day!